

CONTACT

Attleboro, MA 781.738.1335 joshrubino@gmail.com joshrubino.com

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Berlin, Germany Certificate UI Design

Rhode Island School of Design (RISD)

Providence, RI Certificate Graphic Design

Stonehill College

Easton, MA
Bachelor of Arts
Communication, Business Administration

SKILLS

Technical Skills

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Bridge, Adobe Premiere, Sketch, InVision, Allen DataGraph Vinyl Cutter, Mimaki Printing, Laser Etching

Creative Skills

Typography, Layout Design, Color Theory, Problem Solving, Image Retouching, Photography, Writing, Wireframing

Interpersonal Skills

Active Listening, Communication, Teaching, Project Management, Leadership

ABOUT ME

UI/UX designer that keeps the user as the focus of highly functional, intentionally crafted designs. An experienced graphic designer and photographer that understands the power of type and image and making informed choices. Decision maker that leads, listens and learns to get the most out of a brand.

EXPERIENCE

Championship Award Guys Plainville, MA

Graphic Designer 2017–2020

Designed printed and three-dimensional awards in accordance to each client's specifications.

Collaborated with Marketing to create company brochures and other collateral, while maintaining visual representation of the brand.

Point person for all department related issues.

Managed multiple projects simultaneously from concept through completion while working with internal stakeholders and outside vendors to ensure their timely and error-free delivery.

Launched and provided all content for company Instagram account.

Bobbie Bush Photography Salem, MA

Image Retouching Specialist/Associate Photographer 2010–2017
Primary image retoucher of all artwork according to creative specifications and client-requested adjustments, including head swaps and composites.

Partnered with senior photographer to deliver print ready files meeting established guidelines.

Effectively communicated with clients and their representatives as an event photographer documenting significant portions of each event.

Josh Rubino Photography Boston, MA/Providence, RI

Professional Photographer 2008–2017

Successfully recruited and engaged in contracts with clients that included Reebok International, Boston University, Evolve Fitness, TPO Theatre Company, Boston Athletic Association and Toxics Use Reduction Institute for Fayfoto, Apartments.com, OpenPages, Inc., Castile Ventures, MassNetComms, CTI Towers, Young Savants, among others.

Instructor for novice-level photography students in a classroom setting to demonstrate proper technical and creative approaches to photography.